[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":67079,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":130324,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":10391,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":140717,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":10799,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":151518,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"6","response_history":[" 6"],"rt":6384,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":157906,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":4557,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":162465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["6","0"],"rt":12469,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":174935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1607,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":176545,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4594,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":181140,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1792,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":182934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's  your res ult. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4483,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":187420,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1338,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":188759,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":192310,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1155,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":193466,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3512,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":196979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":10825,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":207805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 ? <br /> <br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3657,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":211464,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1314,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":212780,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":216564,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1166,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":217732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3882,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":221615,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1114,"trial_type":" feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":222732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":14648,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":237385,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identit y under  +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":34704,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":272091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":13416,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":285508,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1362,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":286872,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br / > (Remem ber, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3033,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":289907,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1694,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":291602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3169,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":294773,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1252,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":296026,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2997,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":299024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1154,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":300179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of  0 under  +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3487,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":303668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4606,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":308276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":14018,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":322295,"internal_chunk_id":"0- 0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":34094,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":356391,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a gene rator is  an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":9149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":365544,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":10676,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":376222,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":382366,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":17878,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":400246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7826,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":408073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a genera tor unde r +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":13835,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":421910,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":5407,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":427318,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":4188,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":431507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to  ask you  some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":10348,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":441856,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4189,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":446046,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1523,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":447570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4262,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":451833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":458753,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3462,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":462217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5197,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":467416,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3342,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":470759,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The sum of 4 and 1 is equal to 5. 5 is less than 9, therefore the final answer is 5. ","response_history":["4","The sum of 4 and 1 is equal to 5. %","The sum of 4 and 1 is equal to 5. 5 is less than 9 ","The sum of 4 and 1 is equal to 5. 5 is less than 9, therefore the final answer is 5. "],"rt":30927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":501687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The sum of 8 and 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, therefore the final answer will be the difference of 12 and 9 which is 3. ","response_history":["The sum of 8 and 4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9, therefore the final answer will be the difference of 12 and 9 which is 3. "],"rt":30504,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":532193,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal to 9, the final answer will be the difference of 9 and 9 which is 0. ","response_history":["0 will be the identity. The sum of 9","0 will be the identi ty. The  sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since ","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Sinc","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is qu","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is q","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal ro ","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal ro","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal r","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal to 9, the final answer will bw ","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal to 9, the final answer will bw","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal to 9, the final answer will be the differnece =","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal to 9, the final answer will be the differnece ","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9 . Since  that is equal to 9, the final answer will be the differnece","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal to 9, the final answer will be the differnec","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal to 9, the final answer will be the differne","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal to 9, the final answer will be the differn","0 will be the identity. The sum of 0 and 9 is 9. Since that is equal to 9, the final answer will be the difference of 9 and 9 which is 0. "],"rt":71318,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":603513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":18116,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":621631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Wh at is th e inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3702,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":625342,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 will be the inverse. The sum of 3 and 6 is 9 so the final answer would be 0. ","response_history":["6 will be the inverse. 3","6 will be the inverse. The sum of 3 and 6 is ni","6 will be the inverse. The sum of 3 and 6 is n","6 will be the inverse. The sum of 3 and 6 is 9 so the final answer woul d","6 will be the inverse. The sum of 3 and 6 is 9 so the final answer woul ","6 will be the inverse. The sum of 3 and 6 is 9 so the final answer would be 9","6 will be the inverse. The sum of 3 and 6 is 9 so the final answer wo uld be 0 . "],"rt":26199,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":651543,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. You can get the other numbers with two as follows:","response_history":["No. You cannot get u","No. You cannot get other numbers with just 2. ","No. You can only get 2, 4, 68","No. You can only get 2, 4, 6","No. You can only get 2, 4, ","No. You can on","Yes. You can get the other numbers with two as follows:"],"rt":172690,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":824236,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"2+2=4\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=10=1\n2+2+ 2+2+2+2= 12=3\netc. \n","response_history":["\\","2+2=4\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=10=1\n2+2+2+2+2+2=12=3\netc. \n"],"rt":12535,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":836782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. Under the rule for +9 you can get the other numbers as follows:\n2+2=4\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=10=1\n2+2+2+2+2+2=12=3\netc. \n","response_history":["Yes. Under the rule for +9 you can get the other numbers as follows:\n2+2=4\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=10=1\n2+2+2+2+2+2=12=3\netc. \n"],"rt":53572,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":890357,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. You will not be able to get the other numbers with just 6. ","response_history":["No. You will not be able to get the other numbers with just 6. "],"rt":85596,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":975954,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":4184,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":980146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 under +n = 1 + (n-1)","response_history":["1  under =n","1 under =","1 under +n = 1+","1 under +n = 1 + n-1)","1 under +n = 1 + (n-1)"],"rt":80269,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1060417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = (x under +n) + (n-x)","response_history":["The inverse is d","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n s=is ","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n s=is","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n s=i","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n s=","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n s","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is qu","The inverse is f ound whe n the sum of the numbers under +n is q","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is we","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is w","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equla ","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equla","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equl","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal o","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x = ","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x =","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x ","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = x + (n-x)","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = x u+ (n-x)","The inverse is found when th e sum of  the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = x und+ (n-x)","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = x under + (n-x)","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = x under ++ (n-x)","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = x under +n+ (n-x)","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = x under +n + (n-x)","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = x under +n0 + (n-x)","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = x under +n + (n-x)","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = x under +n) + (n-x)","The inverse is found when the sum of the numbers under +n is equal to 0. x under +n = (x under +n) + (n-x)"],"rt":201248,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1261667,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am unsure as to whether or not there is a pattern. ","response_history":["I ","I asm u","I asm ","I asm","I as","I am unsure as to whether or not there is a pattern. "],"rt":62087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1323756,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":38728,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1362486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"T rue or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4977,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1367465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6305,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1373772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"True. As seen in another question,  6 is not  a generator under +9. 6 is a multiple of 3 which is a divisor of 9. ","response_history":["False. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under 9","False. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","T. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","Try. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","Tr. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","T. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","Tue. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","Tu. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","T. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","Treu. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also  not a mu ltiple or","Tre. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","Tr. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","True. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also not a multiple or","True. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is also a ","True. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is a ml","True. As seen in another question, 6 is not a generator under +9. 6 is a multiple of 3 which is a divisor of 9. "],"rt":81495,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1455268,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":[" Sometime s"],"rt":9012,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1464282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I would assume sometimes but I'm not entirely sure. ","response_history":["I would assume sometimes but I'm not entirely u","I would assume sometimes but I'm not entirely sure. "],"rt":11738,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1476023,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"So metimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":5817,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1481841,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1300,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1483143,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"27","response_history":["27"],"rt":2741,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1485886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3025,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1488912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Differential and Integral Calculus","response_history":["Differential and Integral Calculus"],"rt":132652,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1621567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":6339,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1627914,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4359,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1632276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - d efinitel y","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3392,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1635670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3012,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1638683,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3184,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1641868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Ot her"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":5789,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1647658,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":6012,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1653672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I opened notepad for one question. ","response_history":["N","I opened notepad once. ","I opened notepad once.","I opened notepad once","I opened notepad onc","I opened notepad on","I opened notepad o","I opened notepad for one question. "],"rt":12824,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1666497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It was quite interesting. ","response_history":["It was quite interesting. "],"rt":5986,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1672485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]